<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>XR Wordsmiths Solarpunk Storytelling Showcase</title>
    <link>https://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on XR Wordsmiths Solarpunk Storytelling Showcase</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About SolarPunk</title>
      <link>https://example.org/about/solarpunk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/about/solarpunk/</guid>
      <description>Solarpunk is all about envisioning a planetary future in which humanity, non-human nature, and technology co-exist in harmony. It can be described as a social movement and a lifestyle, as well as a genre of literature, art, fashion, music, and architecture.
Solarpunk’s main ethos lies in finding solutions for a more sustainable and egalitarian world through rebellion against the status quo. Its distinctive aesthetics are bright, clean, and futuristic, often reminiscent of sci-fi themes and involving iconography such as vertical gardens, birds of paradise, waterfalls, futuristic architecture, and indigenous art.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About the Artwork</title>
      <link>https://example.org/about/artwork/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/about/artwork/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About the Judges</title>
      <link>https://example.org/about/judges/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/about/judges/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About the Prizes</title>
      <link>https://example.org/about/prizes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/about/prizes/</guid>
      <description>The winning stories from the 2021 Showcase will be published in Solarpunk Magazine, Solarpunk Society Magazine, Shoreline of Infinity Science-Fiction Magazine, by the Rapid Transition Alliance, and in Extinction Rebellion publications. All winning stories are currently being illustrated by a team of artists spread across the globe. The artwork will be published on this website once complete.
Our other 2021 prizes included full scholarships to Terra.do (the world’s first online global climate school), in-person workshops by Taiwanese sustainable design education enterprise TOTES &amp;amp; TEES, interviews and podcast versions of the stories by Solarpunk Magazine, interviews with Ecofictology vlogger Lovis Geier, 1-to-1 mentorship with eco-writer and poet Helen Moore, animal adoption kits, plant seeds, Solarpunk Magazine annual subscriptions, certificates, and of course - books!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About the Showcase</title>
      <link>https://example.org/about/showcase/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/about/showcase/</guid>
      <description>The XR Wordsmiths Solarpunk Storytelling Showcase is Extinction Rebellion’s first global short story contest for all ages.
The project rides the wave of the Solarpunk movement and aims to use the power of collective imagination as a tool against the climate and ecological emergency. Through radical re-imaginings of the world, we can get closer to creating a future that is positive and healthy for all life.
2021’s Showcase was this project’s first iteration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About XR Wordsmiths</title>
      <link>https://example.org/about/xr-wordsmiths/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/about/xr-wordsmiths/</guid>
      <description>We are a band/collective of writers who are deeply concerned with the climate and ecological emergency facing us all. We are a part of Extinction Rebellion, and hail from all over the world.
Our writing is one way we battle against this emergency— we hope it spurs curiosity, concern, inspiration, reflection, love, rage, and also action.
Check out the XR Wordsmiths blog, where you’ll find all kinds of writing and a diversity of voices and styles, to remind us of the diversity of humankind and our beautiful living earth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automata Albatross</title>
      <link>https://example.org/stories/automata-albatross/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/stories/automata-albatross/</guid>
      <description>The albatross almost struck Akila as it fell. With a metallic shriek, it plummeted from the empty gray sky to shatter at her feet, wires spilling onto the slick cement of the sidewalk. She stood frozen in shock as tendrils of steam coolant curled through her braids, its beak chattering eerily as it shuddered into stillness. A dead albatross was very bad luck, her offshore studies professor had told her. Perhaps he would know what to do with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blood Oil</title>
      <link>https://example.org/stories/blood-oil/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/stories/blood-oil/</guid>
      <description>I walk through the tall grass, it whispers against my legs. My bare feet press against the soft soil and I hear Mother Earth calling out to me, crying for help. Along the horizon, I see the oil pipeline cutting across the forest, swaths of trees chopped down in its wake. A scar cutting across Mother Earth, drawing the blood from within her to the surface. Blood flowing forth, a torrent of blood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>City Starlight &amp; The Cemetery</title>
      <link>https://example.org/stories/city-starlight-cemetery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/stories/city-starlight-cemetery/</guid>
      <description>City Starlight
I can feel the anxiety radiating through me as I paddle the kayak with slow, wide motions. What am I anxious about, you ask? Nothing in particular. That’s what is so frustrating about it- I feel it all the time, even on perfectly nice, ordinary days. I take a deep breath and try to absorb some of the tranquility of the environment around me. The sun is almost done rising, the sky a fiery orange, with only the barest strokes of indigo around the edges alluding to the fact that it had been dark just a few minutes ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://example.org/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/contact/</guid>
      <description>If you have any questions or ideas for collaboration,
please reach us at xr-writers@protonmail.com.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Donate</title>
      <link>https://example.org/donate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/donate/</guid>
      <description>The 2021 Solarpunk Storytelling Showcase was only made possible through the incredible hard work and generosity of everyone involved: judges, illustrators, graphic designers, web developers, prize donors - the list goes on.
We were amazed to see how far this project went without any official fundraising, and are excited to see how much bigger and better it can get in later iterations. As such, we have set up a Just Giving Page where you can donate to help fund the next Showcase - any amount appreciated and welcome!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dylan Cooler</title>
      <link>https://example.org/stories/dylan-cooler/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/stories/dylan-cooler/</guid>
      <description>I’m Dylan, the greatest inventor of all time. One of my greatest Inventions is a giant water-powered air conditioner with a global warming detector, I named it- Dylan Cooler! So why did I invent this machine?
I genuinely love animals, especially polar bears. They live in the North Pole where there is a lot of ice. They need this ice to feed, rest and raise families. However the ice is melting because of global warming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gabby&#39;s First Kiss</title>
      <link>https://example.org/stories/gabby/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/stories/gabby/</guid>
      <description>Gabby nearly knocked her mother over as she rushed through the kitchen and out the front door. Outside, she paused to look over the horizon. Her home, like all the homes in Bahía del Paraíso, sat high in the air; protected from the floods that were a regular part of life in their small coastal community. From her perch, she could easily see all the way to the bay. In the early morning sunlight, the mangroves along the water’s edge glowed as if they were on fire.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Green Wall</title>
      <link>https://example.org/stories/green-wall/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/stories/green-wall/</guid>
      <description>The light from the tall window glinted on the pincers. Between their finely-engineered points, Lin held a tiny, red-leaved oxalis. With a purposeful prod, she inserted it into the wad of sphagnum moss where the other red-leaved species were already taking root. Further back along the wall, where she had first begun, tides of green tendrils lapped against jade fractals. Glossy weeping figs sheltered verdant ferns, whose close-held scent reminded Lin of woodland streams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Green Witch</title>
      <link>https://example.org/stories/green-witch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/stories/green-witch/</guid>
      <description>Between sunset and starlight spans the twilight, and that is when we witches gather to dance in the garden. Live by the sun, love by the moon, so goes the old saying. A catchy soundbite, a t-shirt slogan, but truer now than ever before, as the solar panels swallow greedily the last peach-red-golden rays on the horizon, as the city sighs its relief and prepares to settle into slumber. The suburbs come alive with a patchwork of lights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hanging Gardens of Babylon</title>
      <link>https://example.org/stories/hanging-gardens/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/stories/hanging-gardens/</guid>
      <description>“What we’re looking at here,” he pulled the map down slightly, “is the only man-made wonder of the world to exist twice. Every other thing on this old list has been destroyed.”
We both took a look at the gates guarding the Hanging Gardens of Babylon. The posts were clearly composed of scrap metal forged into single, twisting rods. The gates reached high above our heads, weaving into each other like so many gleaming branches.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Home</title>
      <link>https://example.org/home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/home/</guid>
      <description>XR Wordsmiths</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Honourable Mentions</title>
      <link>https://example.org/stories/honorable/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/stories/honorable/</guid>
      <description>Utopia in the Sewers
by Özkan Akman
Green Wall
Clare Harvey
The Well-Trodden Path
by Tom Jubert
Rooted Ritual
by Charlie McKay Seaweed
by Hazel Morfett
The Hanging Gardens of Babylon
by Rebekah Neuberger
Meeting at the Giant Mushroom
by Jeremy Parker
Sooty
by by Luke Lanyon-Hog</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hospitalized in Utopia</title>
      <link>https://example.org/stories/hospitalized-utopia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/stories/hospitalized-utopia/</guid>
      <description>Diana looked out the window at the sky. It was a good sky, she liked looking at it, but she couldn’t look at much else. If she turned her head the other way she could see only pale blue walls, medical equipment, and a glimpse of that machine in the hallway that went beep! beep! beep! She couldn’t imagine what it did—and she had tried.
Supposedly her window actually had a lovely view of half the green city.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meeting at the Giant Mushroom</title>
      <link>https://example.org/stories/meeting-mushrooms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/stories/meeting-mushrooms/</guid>
      <description>Lisa Kendrick brushed down her smart, grey skirt suit, then smoothed her perfectly styled hair. Pausing, she checked her makeup and gave her hair a second glance, then she nodded, satisfied that she still looked like she’d just stepped out of a salon. Then she stopped and thought. Then she sat down.
“I’m overdressed,” she told herself. Damn. She hadn’t wanted to fret, but there she was, fretting. She wanted to impress but she was probably going about it in completely the wrong way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Return to Kiribati</title>
      <link>https://example.org/stories/return-kiribati/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/stories/return-kiribati/</guid>
      <description>Only the cold, untwinkling speck of a space station pierced the darkness between the thinning cumulus and the churning ink-black sea.
The storm sail billowed and creaked, water thundered like rapids between the three hulls, and Kraken hydrofoiled a metre clear of the water, slicing through the detritus of coconuts and disintegrating plastic that had been whipped into a seething broth by the Pacific cyclone wind. My eyes combed the ebony veils for signs of pursuit, but the outcasts’ ramshackle vessel couldn’t have made it through.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rooted Ritual</title>
      <link>https://example.org/stories/rooted-ritual/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/stories/rooted-ritual/</guid>
      <description>Paulo awoke to the sound of sizzling tomatoes being cooked by his grandmother in the kitchen of their two-bedroom apartment. Several seconds of serene silence passed before she sweetly beckoned him for breakfast.
“Paulo…. Paulo” she called, followed by several other soft murmurings that he couldn’t quite discern.
The air was crisp as beams of light filtered through the mosaic gaps of his slightly ajar window. He stretched, stirred, twisted and eventually rose to peer out across the vast landscape of pinkish clouds that were warmed by a golden coat from the early morning sun.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Runners Up</title>
      <link>https://example.org/stories/runners-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/stories/runners-up/</guid>
      <description>Hospitalized in Utopia
by Caroline Ailanthus
Wall of Flowers
by Septimus Crowe Automata Albatross
by Robin Happel
Return to Kiribati
by Alexandra Porter Green Witch
by Katrina Townsend</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seaweed</title>
      <link>https://example.org/stories/seaweed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/stories/seaweed/</guid>
      <description>The dark eye of the whale focused contemplatively on the thick clumps of seaweed streaming past. The fronds brushed up against her skin, which like her eye, took in the colour and shape of the fresh green plants. Blinking slowly, she rolled towards the surface, pulled a deep gasp of empty air into her lungs, turned her fins, and directed the movement and power of her body downwards.
Below in the depths, her family circled, noses touching tails, grandmothers of hundreds of years covered in thousands of barnacles brushing up against last year’s babies, smooth as silk and bright pale grey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sooty</title>
      <link>https://example.org/stories/sooty/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/stories/sooty/</guid>
      <description>If there was one word to describe the city it was small. Tiny compared to the Fuel Era cities. Or at least the ruins of them. In the centre were the towers and the bigger buildings, not too dissimilar to the old cities. Just smaller. Every building had either a wind turbine on it or tracking solar array. When viewed from a distance it looked like a collection of potted flowers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Future School</title>
      <link>https://example.org/stories/future-school/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/stories/future-school/</guid>
      <description>Nowadays, students do not enjoy school much because it is boring. So a lot of teachers are determined to make the school a fun place, while keeping it safe and eco-friendly. But how? We’ll find out!
Outside there will be an invisible protection zone, when you want to go to the school there will be fingerprint recognition to check if it is you, also there will be a hand sanitizer inside.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Happy Wolf</title>
      <link>https://example.org/stories/happy-wolf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/stories/happy-wolf/</guid>
      <description>My name is Axel. I like being a wolf because I have a lovely forest with Evergreen trees. Like Christmas trees. And it is very cold because I am in the Arctic. I like the Evergreen trees because they keep us healthy.
Now that we’re not being hunted we get to run around and be more safe. The snow is thick and white and it feels rough. We get to play games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Old Man and the Bird</title>
      <link>https://example.org/stories/old-man-bird/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/stories/old-man-bird/</guid>
      <description>It had been years since the bird heard the last trucks, saws, and men cutting down the trees, killing its friends, and destroying its home. The colorful bird was singing on its tree, waiting for the Old Man to tell him stories. The Old Man told him about men’s cities: lush forests of blue, green, and gold, far away from the bird’s home. The stories were so different from the tales of the bird’s grandfather, who told him about dark, grey places of fear and misery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Park</title>
      <link>https://example.org/stories/the-park/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/stories/the-park/</guid>
      <description>The child’s face was cold, with a coating of frost and an icicle hanging off the end of her chin.
The sun glinted off her forehead in fits and starts as it peeked through the clouds, but it was too little to warm her.
It was January, after all, and it had been a cloudy winter.
Jules always cut through the park on her way to work, but she liked it best this time of year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Singer of Seeds</title>
      <link>https://example.org/stories/singer-of-seeds/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/stories/singer-of-seeds/</guid>
      <description>Maïa climbs up the ladder and tries to sit next to me with as little noise as possible.
“You’re late,” I mutter, and it comes out more annoyed than I am.
“I know,” she whispers, crossing her legs on the sandwood boards to my mat, as she has forgotten hers again.
We stare at the landscape before us, a hand risen up to our faces, covering the left eye. Our right eye is fixed on that jagged line of mountain crests on the horizon, where the purple haze is shifting into a warm peach light.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Tides Rolled In</title>
      <link>https://example.org/stories/tides-rolled/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/stories/tides-rolled/</guid>
      <description>The tides rolled in. The tides rolled out. It was as simple as that. And in that simplicity there was power. Enough to light entire cities, even, not that Afton knew personally. Her little village did just fine, roaming the waves, but in her thirteen years she’d never seen the capital of the Floating Republic. She’d never walked on sidewalks so steady it was said you couldn’t even feel the rocking of the waves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Well-Trodden Path</title>
      <link>https://example.org/stories/well-trodden/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/stories/well-trodden/</guid>
      <description>“Where are they?” asked Blue, transferring into the cockpit. “How worried are we?” “They’re post-nuclear, pre-Universal,” replied Grey, projecting a zoomed-in view of the industrial complexes which studded the blue/beige planet they were orbiting. Blue performed the guttural vibrations which in their culture meant frustration, and complained: “Just once, I’d like to find a people we can talk with who don’t yet have the means and inclination to incinerate everything.”</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Utopia in the Sewers</title>
      <link>https://example.org/stories/utopia-sewers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/stories/utopia-sewers/</guid>
      <description>September 28th, Daylight. They have overtaken the surface for quite some time now. Their calendars say the year is 2089, ours 58. I do not know which one’s true. We are safe underground in a place the surface people call Esenyurt. They don’t come down, we don’t go up. Sewers run deep. They don’t allow us at the surface of the city. They send their nuclear waste and garbage down here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wall of Flowers</title>
      <link>https://example.org/stories/wall-flowers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/stories/wall-flowers/</guid>
      <description>Never do this. I&amp;rsquo;m not the most outdoorsy person, but even I know that if you&amp;rsquo;re lost and alone in the woods, it&amp;rsquo;s a bad idea to scoff a bunch of unidentified mushrooms. The thing is, I just couldn&amp;rsquo;t help myself. The afternoon sun slanting through the trees was so golden, the colours of the autumn leaves so alluring, that I had wandered further and further from the trail; and when I came to a clearing filled with shifting, dappled light and saw the clump of small, pale blue mushrooms gleaming like strange gemstones, it seemed the most natural thing in the world to nibble one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Where Giants Will Stand</title>
      <link>https://example.org/stories/giants-stand/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/stories/giants-stand/</guid>
      <description>Cora and Rosa caught me in the garden. They rode their bikes under the arched passion fruit vines and into our driveway. I had just finished pruning the tomatoes. Knees achy, I welcomed their timing.
“Hi Grandpa!” Rosa yelled as she raced past the olive guild and the perfumed loquats.
“Happy birthday, my sweet child!”
She laid her bike down, hopped a garden bed and smothered me.
“Your grandpop and I made you a present,” I whispered conspiratorially in her ear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WINNERS 11 &amp; Under</title>
      <link>https://example.org/stories/11-and-under/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/stories/11-and-under/</guid>
      <description>The Happy Wolf 
by Mikhayel, age 6. London, England
Dylan Cooler
by Dylan, age 9. Taipei, Taiwan
The Future School 
by Liz, age 10. Taipei, Taiwan</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WINNERS 12 - 18</title>
      <link>https://example.org/stories/12-18-winners/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/stories/12-18-winners/</guid>
      <description>City Starlight &amp; The Cemetery
by Katrina Eilender. New Jersey, U.S.A.
The Old Man and the Bird 
by Aël Magnard. Paris, France.
Blood Oil
by Rebecca &#34;Reb&#34; Spring. Washington DC, U.S.A</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WINNERS 19 &amp; Over</title>
      <link>https://example.org/stories/18-ov-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/stories/18-ov-1/</guid>
      <description>Gabby&#39;s First Kiss
by Joe Tankersley. Florida, U.S.A. Where Giants Will Stand
by Spencer R. Scott. California, U.S.A
The Tides Rolled In
by Chris Muscato. Colorado, U.S.A.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>XR Wordsmiths&#39; Top Picks</title>
      <link>https://example.org/stories/xr-top-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/stories/xr-top-1/</guid>
      <description>The Singer of Seeds
by Leda Baöl. Torino, Italy / Amsterdam, The Netherlands.
The Park
by Adam Marx. Borehamwood, England. </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
