<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About on XR Wordsmiths Solarpunk Storytelling Showcase</title>
    <link>https://example.org/about/</link>
    <description>Recent content in About on XR Wordsmiths Solarpunk Storytelling Showcase</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://example.org/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About SolarPunk</title>
      <link>https://example.org/about/solarpunk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/about/solarpunk/</guid>
      <description>Solarpunk is all about envisioning a planetary future in which humanity, non-human nature, and technology co-exist in harmony. It can be described as a social movement and a lifestyle, as well as a genre of literature, art, fashion, music, and architecture.
Solarpunk’s main ethos lies in finding solutions for a more sustainable and egalitarian world through rebellion against the status quo. Its distinctive aesthetics are bright, clean, and futuristic, often reminiscent of sci-fi themes and involving iconography such as vertical gardens, birds of paradise, waterfalls, futuristic architecture, and indigenous art.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About the Artwork</title>
      <link>https://example.org/about/artwork/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/about/artwork/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About the Judges</title>
      <link>https://example.org/about/judges/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/about/judges/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About the Prizes</title>
      <link>https://example.org/about/prizes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/about/prizes/</guid>
      <description>The winning stories from the 2021 Showcase will be published in Solarpunk Magazine, Solarpunk Society Magazine, Shoreline of Infinity Science-Fiction Magazine, by the Rapid Transition Alliance, and in Extinction Rebellion publications. All winning stories are currently being illustrated by a team of artists spread across the globe. The artwork will be published on this website once complete.
Our other 2021 prizes included full scholarships to Terra.do (the world’s first online global climate school), in-person workshops by Taiwanese sustainable design education enterprise TOTES &amp;amp; TEES, interviews and podcast versions of the stories by Solarpunk Magazine, interviews with Ecofictology vlogger Lovis Geier, 1-to-1 mentorship with eco-writer and poet Helen Moore, animal adoption kits, plant seeds, Solarpunk Magazine annual subscriptions, certificates, and of course - books!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About the Showcase</title>
      <link>https://example.org/about/showcase/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/about/showcase/</guid>
      <description>The XR Wordsmiths Solarpunk Storytelling Showcase is Extinction Rebellion’s first global short story contest for all ages.
The project rides the wave of the Solarpunk movement and aims to use the power of collective imagination as a tool against the climate and ecological emergency. Through radical re-imaginings of the world, we can get closer to creating a future that is positive and healthy for all life.
2021’s Showcase was this project’s first iteration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About XR Wordsmiths</title>
      <link>https://example.org/about/xr-wordsmiths/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/about/xr-wordsmiths/</guid>
      <description>We are a band/collective of writers who are deeply concerned with the climate and ecological emergency facing us all. We are a part of Extinction Rebellion, and hail from all over the world.
Our writing is one way we battle against this emergency— we hope it spurs curiosity, concern, inspiration, reflection, love, rage, and also action.
Check out the XR Wordsmiths blog, where you’ll find all kinds of writing and a diversity of voices and styles, to remind us of the diversity of humankind and our beautiful living earth.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
